ASFAQ MAHMUD SAIF

Software Engineer | Database Engineer



Phone: +8801618550633 Date of birth: 15-08-2002

Email: mahmudsaifx@gmail.com LinkedIn: linked.in/mahmudsaifx

Address: Daudkandi, Comilla Github: github.com/saifx

About me

I am a software engineer specializing in back-end development and Database engineering. Experienced with all stages of software development cycle for dynamic projects. Well-versed in numerous programming language including C/C++, Java, Python. Strong background in project management.

Work History

2023-01 - 2024-01	Sr. Software Engineer Brain Craft Solution , Dhanmondi, Dhaka
2022-01 - 2023-01	Jr. Database Engineer Enosis Solution , Gulshan , Dhaka
2020-04 - 2022-01	Jr. Software Engineer Cefalo Bangladesh Ltd. , Dhaka

Education

2016	-	2020	Computer Science and Engineering Khulna University of Engineering and Technology • CGPA – 3.42 out of 4
2014	-	2016	Higher Secondary School Certificate Saint Joseph Higher Secondary School, Dhaka GPA – 5.0 out of 5
2007	-	2014	Secondary School Certificate Comilla Zilla School, Comilla GPA – 5.0 out of 5

ASFAQ MAHMUD SAIF

Software Engineer | Database Engineer



Skills

- Data Structure and algorithms
- Object Oriented Programming (OOP)
- Android Development
- Web Development
- Machine Learning
- Image Processing
- Database
- Flutter
- iOS development

Programming Languages

- C / C++
- Python
- PHP
- Java
- Kotlin
- Dart
- Swift

Languages

- English
- Bangla
- Spanish

Recommendations

1. Dr. K. M. Azharul Hasan

Professor

Dept of CSE, KUET

2. Sunanda Das

Assistant Professor

Dept of CSE, KUET